<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Hero Me</string>

    <!-- TODO: Remove or change this placeholder text -->
    <string name="spiderman">SPIDERMAN</string>
    <string name="turtles">TURTLES</string>
    <string name="superman">SUPERMAN</string>
    <string name="lazer">LAZERMAN</string>
    <string name="thor">THOR</string>
    <string name="hulk">HULK</string>

    <string name="spiderman_story">In Forest Hills, Queens, New York, high school student Peter Parker is a science-whiz orphan
                                   living with his Uncle Ben and Aunt May. As depicted in Amazing Fantasy #15 (Aug. 1962), he is
                                   bitten by a radioactive spider (erroneously classified as an insect in the panel) at a science
                                   exhibit and "acquires the agility and proportionate strength of an arachnid". Along with super
                                   strength, Parker gains the ability to adhere to walls and ceilings. Through his native knack for science,
                                   he develops a gadget that lets him fire adhesive webbing of his own design through small, wrist-mounted barrels. </string>
    <string name="superman_story">Superman is born on an alien world to a technologically advanced species that resembles humans.
                                  When his world is on the verge of destruction, his father, a scientist, places his infant son alone
                                  in a spaceship that takes him to Earth. The earliest newspaper strips name the planet "Krypton", the
                                  baby "Kal-L", and his biological parents "Jor-L" and "Lora"; their names become "Jor-el", and "Lara"
                                  in a 1942 spinoff novel by George Lowther. The ship lands in the American countryside, where the baby
                                  is adopted by the Kents. </string>
    <string name="turtles_story">The Teenage Mutant Ninja Turtles first appeared in an American comic book published by Mirage Studios
                                 in 1984 in Dover, New Hampshire. The concept arose from a humorous drawing sketched out by Eastman during
                                 a casual evening of brainstorming and bad television with Laird.[3] Using money from a tax refund, together
                                 with a loan from Eastman’s uncle, the young artists self-published a single-issue comic intended to parody
                                 four of the most popular comics of the early 1980s </string>
    <string name="thor_story">During the events of the 2010 "Siege" storyline, Thor defends Asgard against an invasion by Norman Osborn
                              and his Dark Avengers. Although the invasion force is ultimately defeated, Asgard itself is toppled by the
                              Sentry, who also kills Loki. Thor then kills the Sentry. Subsequently, the Superhuman Registration Act is
                              repealed and Thor joins the rebranded Avengers, who had come to his aid during the battle.The next day Balder
                              lifts Thor\s exile and appoints Thor as his adviser. </string>
    <string name="hulk_story">During the experimental detonation of a gamma bomb, scientist Bruce Banner saves teenager Rick Jones who has
                              driven onto the testing field; Banner pushes Jones into a trench to save him, but is hit with the blast, absorbing
                              massive amounts of gamma radiation. He awakens later seemingly unscathed, but that night transforms into a lumbering
                              grey form. A pursuing soldier dubs the creature a "hulk". Originally, Banner transformed into the Hulk at sunset
                              and reverted at sunrise. Banner was cured in The Incredible Hulk #4, but chose to restore Hulk\s powers with Banner\s
                              intelligence. </string>
    <string name="lazer_story">Cyclops first appeared in X-Men #1 (September 1963). He was created by Stan Lee and Jack Kirby, and has
                               been a mainstay character of the X-Men series. Lee said that Cyclops and the Beast were his two favorite
                               X-Men, elaborating that "I love tortured heroes - and he was tortured because he couldn\t control his power.
                               "Originally dubbed Slim Summers, by X-Men #3 his name was changed to Scott, with \Slim\ becoming a nickname.
                               [citation needed] Scott is the first of the X-Men recruited by Professor X; Xavier hand-picks Scott to lead
                                his X-Men, and to carry on the legacy of his mutant-human-harmony ideals. </string>


</resources>
